Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series E: Miscellaneous, 1938-01-1939-09
  - Photo Unit #: E1189 Captain Dunbar and Major José Antonio Valledor, Gandesa [with two others], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1671)
  - Photo Unit #: E1190 Captain Rollin Dart, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1672)
  - Photo Unit #: E1191 Morris Stamm and John Coon, Lincoln-Washington, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1673)
    Available Formats: Original Negative; Copy Negative; Print
  - Photo Unit #: E1192 Loading a machine-gun belt, Gandesa [2 soldiers], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1674)
  - Photo Unit #: E1193 Patrick Roosevelt and Pete [?], with machine gun, Gandesa, Lincoln-Washington, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1675)
  - Photo Unit #: E1194 Abraham Copeland of Transmiciones [Transmissions], Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1676)
  - Photo Unit #: E1195 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1677)
  - Photo Unit #: E1196 Lincoln-Washington Battalion David (Red) Drummond, Nick Pappas, Eluard Luchell McDaniels, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1678)
  - Photo Unit #: E1197 Captured Machine-Gunner, Lincoln-Washington Battalion Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1679)
  - Photo Unit #: E1198 Sergeant Guy Thorpe and Sergeant Max Bowers, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1680)
  - Photo Unit #: E1200 Cabo Narciso Gonzales, Adjuntant Lieutenant Jack Cooper, Jefe, Rafael Maltes, Commissar, Spanish M. E. [?] Company, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1681)
  - Photo Unit #: E1201 Herman (Gabby) Klein sleeping, Lincoln-Washington Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0106)
  - Photo Unit #: E1203 David Lipton firing rifle, Lincoln-Washington, Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1682)
  - Photo Unit #: E1204 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1683)
  - Photo Unit #: E1206 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Company 3, Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1684)
  - Photo Unit #: E1207 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1685)
  - Photo Unit #: E1209 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Gandesa, Aug 1939 (Item 11-1686)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/14)
  - Photo Unit #: E1210 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Gandesa, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1687)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/55)
  - Photo Unit #: E1237 Water tank, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1688)
  - Photo Unit #: E1240 Cubans, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1689)
  - Photo Unit #: E1241 Cubans, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1690)
  - Photo Unit #: E1242 Sandor Voros, Miles Tomalin, Ernest Mahoney, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1691)
  - Photo Unit #: E1244 Lincoln-Washington group, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0107)
  - Photo Unit #: E1245 Alvah Bessie and Edwin Rolfe, Lincoln-Washington, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0108)
  - Photo Unit #: E1246 Aaron Lopoff, Alvah Bessie, Rico Rusciano at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1692)
  - Photo Unit #: E1247 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1693)
  - Photo Unit #: E1248 Ernst Toller and David Roosevelt, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1694)
  - Photo Unit #: E1249 Ernst Toller, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0109)
  - Photo Unit #: E1250 Lincoln-Washington group playing cards, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1695)
  - Photo Unit #: E1251 Lincoln-Washington observers, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1696)
  - Photo Unit #: E1252 Lincoln-Washington positions at rest, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1697)
  - Photo Unit #: E1257 Tony Pujol digging refugio, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0110)
  - Photo Unit #: E1258 David Gordon, Maurice Miller, Edwin Rolfe, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0513)
  - Photo Unit #: E1259 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, runners, etc., Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0514)
  - Photo Unit #: E1260 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] group, Thomas Norton in center, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0515)
  - Photo Unit #: E1262 Group from Williamsburg, New York, Lincoln-Washington, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1698)
  - Photo Unit #: E1265 MacKenzie-Papineau Company, 5 citiations: Deszo Beke, Jose Asenci, Yaigve Lekto, Toivo Suni, undated (Item 11-1699)
  - Photo Unit #: E1268 59th Battalion, Company 2, citations: Luis Peraza, Lieutenant Geronimo Lopez, Pedro Aquilla Rio, Corbera, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0516)
  - Photo Unit #: E1276 Salvador Plana, James Bourne, William Griffiths, Mora de Ebro, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0517)
  - Photo Unit #: E1278 Some of the Commissariat, Mora de Ebro, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0518)
  - Photo Unit #: E1283 Waiting to cross the Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0519)
  - Photo Unit #: E1285 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0520)
  - Photo Unit #: E1286 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0521)
  - Photo Unit #: E1287 Building foot bridge across Ebro [carrying lumber], June 25, 1938 (Item 11-1869)
  - Photo Unit #: E1288 Building foot bridge across Ebro [sections of bridge piled on river bank] (Item 11-1870)
  - Photo Unit #: E1289 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0522)
  - Photo Unit #: E1292 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0523)
  - Photo Unit #: E1293 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0524)
  - Photo Unit #: E1302 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-1700)
  - Photo Unit #: E1303 Stretching the cable across Ebro, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0525)
  - Photo Unit #: E1305 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0526)
  - Photo Unit #: E1306 Crossing the Ebro [placing the lines] (Item 11-1877)
  - Photo Unit #: E1307 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0527)
  - Photo Unit #: E1308 Building foot bridge across Ebro, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1206)
  - Photo Unit #: E1309 Building the foot bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0528)
  - Photo Unit #: E1312 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1207)
  - Photo Unit #: E1313 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-1701)
  - Photo Unit #: E1315 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [landing in a boat] (Item 11-1876)
  - Photo Unit #: E1317 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-1702)
  - Photo Unit #: E1318 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge [men walking to boats] (Item 11-1871)
  - Photo Unit #: E1320 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, another in background] (Item 11-1872)
  - Photo Unit #: E1321 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0529)
  - Photo Unit #: E1322 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1703)
  - Photo Unit #: E1323 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 25, 1938 (Item 11-0530)
  - Photo Unit #: E1325 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0531)
  - Photo Unit #: E1328 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0532)
  - Photo Unit #: E1333 Crossing Ebro by boat and bridge, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0533)
  - Photo Unit #: E1336 Crossing the Ebro by boat and bridge[launching a boat, close-up view] (Item 11-1873)
  - Photo Unit #: E1338 Crossing the Ebro by pontoon bridge (Item 11-1874)
  - Photo Unit #: E1340 William Allander and his truck after bombing, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0534)
  - Photo Unit #: E1341 Bill Allander and his truck after bombing [with man unloading a box], undated (Item 11-1704)
  - Photo Unit #: E1344 Captured rifles, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0535)
  - Photo Unit #: E1349 Corbera recaptured, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0536)
  - Photo Unit #: E1350 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0537)
  - Photo Unit #: E1354 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated (Item 11-0538)
  - Photo Unit #: E1355 Shelling near Lincoln-Washington positions, undated (Item 11-0539)
  - Photo Unit #: E1358 Unexploded Shell, undated (Item 11-0540)
  - Photo Unit #: E1359 Drawing water at MacKenzie-Papineau [?] [donkey with several soldiers], undated (Item 11-1705)
  - Photo Unit #: E1361 Lincoln-Washington Battalion out for rest, undated (Item 11-0541)
  - Photo Unit #: E1362 Heliograf squad [3 men], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1706)
  - Photo Unit #: E1363 Heliograf squad, Jul 1938 (Item 11-1208)
  - Photo Unit #: E1365 Heliograph squad, Russell Stephens [3 men w/equipement], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1707)
  - Photo Unit #: E1367 Heliograf squad, Jul 1938 (Item 11-0542)
  - Photo Unit #: E1368 Doctor Julius Hene, Major Edward Cecil [?] Smith, Hamish Frazer, undated (Item 11-1708)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/43)
  - Photo Unit #: E1371 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0543)
  - Photo Unit #: E1372 Washing up, undated (Item 11-0544)
  - Photo Unit #: E1374 William Van Felix and Ernest Amatniek, undated (Item 11-0545)
  - Photo Unit #: E1375 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0546)
  - Photo Unit #: E1376 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0547)
  - Photo Unit #: E1377 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0548)
  - Photo Unit #: E1378 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0549)
  - Photo Unit #: E1379 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0550)
  - Photo Unit #: E1380 Lincoln-Washington wounded, undated (Item 11-0551)
  - Photo Unit #: E1383 Loading machine-gun belts, undated (Item 11-1209)
  - Photo Unit #: E1384 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, undated (Item 11-0552)
  - Photo Unit #: E1386 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0553)
  - Photo Unit #: E1387 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], George Watt and Major Milton Wolff, with others, at Gandesa Front, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1709)
  - Photo Unit #: E1395 Brigade Sanidad [Health], undated (Item 11-0554)
  - Photo Unit #: E1399 Brigade Sanidad [Health], undated (Item 11-0555)
  - Photo Unit #: E1401 Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0556)
  - Photo Unit #: E1402 John Gates, undated (Item 11-1210)
  - Photo Unit #: E1405 Volunteer Shaving [another] (Item 11-1878)
  - Photo Unit #: E1407 Brigade Topographers, undated (Item 11-0557)
  - Photo Unit #: E1408 Brigade Topographers, undated (Item 11-0558)
  - Photo Unit #: E1412 Fascist prisoners, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0559)
  - Photo Unit #: E1414 Fascist prisoners, undated (Item 11-1710)
  - Photo Unit #: E1415 Fascist prisoners, undated (Item 11-0560)
  - Photo Unit #: E1417 Fascist prisoners, undated (Item 11-0561)
  - Photo Unit #: E1423 15 International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0562)
  - Photo Unit #: E1428 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0563)
  - Photo Unit #: E1429 Lincoln-Washington Estado Mayor [Headquarters], undated (Item 11-0564)
  - Photo Unit #: E1430 Lincoln-Washington Transmiciones [Transmissions], undated (Item 11-0565)
  - Photo Unit #: E1434 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, group photograph, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1847)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/50)
  - Photo Unit #: E1436 Soldier, reading mail, undated (Item 11-1211)
  - Photo Unit #: E1439 School kids and James Bourne, undated (Item 11-0566)
  - Photo Unit #: E1440 MacKenzie-Papineau, Edward Cecil Smith [playing checkers], Jul 1938 (Item 11-1711)
  - Photo Unit #: E1442 Building cave room at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1712)
  - Photo Unit #: E1445 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] Position, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1713)
  - Photo Unit #: E1446 Headquarters, Sierra Pandols, undated (Item 11-1714)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/89)
  - Photo Unit #: E1451 15th International Brigade action shot, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1715)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/59)
  - Photo Unit #: E1452 MacKenzie-Papineau, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1716)
  - Photo Unit #: E1455 MacKenzie-Papineau fortifying, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1717)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/49)
  - Photo Unit #: E1456 Soldier reading in trench (Item 11-1879)
  - Photo Unit #: E1457 MacKenzie-Papineau fortifying, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1718)
  - Photo Unit #: E1458 Henry Mack at Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Aug 1938 (Item 11-0111)
  - Photo Unit #: E1459 MacKenzie-Papineau, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0112)
  - Photo Unit #: E1460 Major Edward Cecil [?] Smith at phone, MacKenzie-Papineau Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1719)
  - Photo Unit #: E1461 Officers at MacKenzie-Papineau Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0113)
  - Photo Unit #: E1462 Frank Rogers and [?], MacKenzie-Papineau Commissars, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1720)
  - Photo Unit #: E1463 Group of MacKenzie-Papineau, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1721)
  - Photo Unit #: E1464 Matthew Mattison of MacKenzie-Papineau cutting tree down, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1722)
  - Photo Unit #: E1465 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Sierra Pandols [2 soldiers], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1723)
  - Photo Unit #: E1466 MacKenzie-Papineau, Sierra Pandols, undated (Item 11-1724)
  - Photo Unit #: E1467 MacKenzie-Papineau, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1725)
  - Photo Unit #: E1468 MacKenzie-Papineau, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1726)
  - Photo Unit #: E1469 MacKenzie-Papineau firing trench mortar, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1727)
  - Photo Unit #: E1470 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, rifleman, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1728)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/46)
  - Photo Unit #: E1471 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, fortifying, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1729)
  - Photo Unit #: E1472 Fascist planes, Sierra Pandols [long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1730)
  - Photo Unit #: E1473 Bombing on horizon seen from Sierra Pandols [long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1731)
  - Photo Unit #: E1474 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [2 soldiers, long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1732)
  - Photo Unit #: E1475 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [2 soldiers, long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1733)
  - Photo Unit #: E1476 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [2 soldiers, at stone wall], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1734)
  - Photo Unit #: E1477 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [soldier, long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1735)
  - Photo Unit #: E1478 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [landscape, long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1736)
  - Photo Unit #: E1479 British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [landscape, long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1737)
  - Photo Unit #: E1480 British Battalion Group, Company 2, Sierra Pandols [4 soldiers, close-up], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1738)
  - Photo Unit #: E1482 British Battalion, Jose Tecle, Sierra Pandols [rifleman], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1739)
  - Photo Unit #: E1483 British Battalion, armory, Sierra Pandols [3 soldiers with weapons and sandbags], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1740)
  - Photo Unit #: E1484 British Battalion, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sierra Pandols [group of soldiers sitting, one with bandaged head], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1741)
  - Photo Unit #: E1484 Estado Mayor [Headquarters], British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [group of soldiers sitting, one iwth bandaged head], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1802)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/14)
  - Photo Unit #: E1485 British Battalion group, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1742)
  - Photo Unit #: E1486 British Battalion, runners, etc. Plana Mayor, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1743)
  - Photo Unit #: E1487 Fascists bombing Corbera, British Battalion, Sierra Pandols [long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1744)
  - Photo Unit #: E1488 Fascists bombing Corbera, Sierra Pandols; [smoke rising over hills], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1745)
  - Photo Unit #: E1489 Fascists bombing Corbera, Sierra Pandols [long view], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1746)
  - Photo Unit #: E1490 Fascists bombing Corbera, Sierra Pandols; [smoke rising over hills], Aug 1938 (Item 11-1747)
  - Photo Unit #: E1491 Lincoln-Washington group, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1748)
  - Photo Unit #: E1492 Lincoln-Washington group, Company 3 [?], Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1749)
  - Photo Unit #: E1493 Grave of Joe Bianca, Lincoln-Washington, Aug 1938 (Item 11-0114)
  - Photo Unit #: E1494 Grave of Joe Bianca, Lincoln-Washington, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1750)
  - Photo Unit #: E1495 Monument to fallen comrades and grave of Captain Egon Schmidt, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1783)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/21)
  - Photo Unit #: E1496 Monument to fallen comrades, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1751)
  - Photo Unit #: E1497 Monument to fallen comrades, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1752)
  - Photo Unit #: E1498 Monument to fallen comrades, Sierra Pandols, Aug 1938 (Item 11-1784)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/22)
  - Photo Unit #: E1500 Harry Pollitt dining at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Sep 1938 (Item 11-1757)
    (Moscow Number: 5/176/4)
  - Photo Unit #: E1504 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at lunch, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1212)
  - Photo Unit #: E1505 Battalion Commissars and Major José Antonio Valledor, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1753)
  - Photo Unit #: E1509 Siesta (Commissariat), Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0567)
  - Photo Unit #: E1512 Company 4, Lincoln-Washington, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0568)
  - Photo Unit #: E1517 [Training:] MacKenzie-Papineau Company 1 [or Lincoln Battalion?], digging fox holes, Sierra Pandols [3 soldiers], Sep 1938 (Item 11-1754)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/35)
  - Photo Unit #: E1518 Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Morris Colow, Thomas Lyons, Lieutenant Hans Kalbschmidt, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1846)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/45)
  - Photo Unit #: E1519 MacKenzie-Papineau resting [in a grove], Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-1296)
  - Photo Unit #: E1520 Lincoln-Washington group, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0569)
  - Photo Unit #: E1533 Alvah Bessie and Ronald Bates, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0570)
  - Photo Unit #: E1534 MacKenzie-Papineau olive grove, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0571)
  - Photo Unit #: E1535 MacKenzie-Papineau group playing cards, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0572)
  - Photo Unit #: E1536 Meeting of Battalion Commissars, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0573)
  - Photo Unit #: E1538 Company 3, Lincoln-Washington (out of focus), Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0574)
  - Photo Unit #: E1539 Company 3, Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0575)
  - Photo Unit #: E1540 William N. Miller of Lincoln-Washington, and Harry Randall, Comisariado [Commissariat], Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0576)
  - Photo Unit #: E1541 Lincoln-Washington Sanidad [Health], Corbera, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0577)
  - Photo Unit #: E1542 Lincoln-Washington comrades watching planes, Sep 1938 (Item 11-0578)
- Series F. Films, circa 1937-1938
  Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
  Access copies for some films may be available by appointment for reading room viewing only. Please contact the Tamiment Library & Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives for more information and to schedule an appointment, tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu or 212-998-2630.
  This series consists of three black-and-white 16 mm reels shot by Harry Randall during the Spanish Civil War. The films document the men and women who volunteered to participate in the conflict, either as members of the International Brigades or the affiliated medical services. The films capture a wide range of footage, including camp sites, military preparations, weather conditions, the landscape of the Spanish countryside, the administration of medical aid, and daily activities such as eating, bathing, sleeping, reading, and writing letters. The films also show the war’s destruction, featuring numerous damaged buildings and structures.
  - Untitled Film Footage: Reel 1, 1937-1938; 1 Reels 16 mm; duration: 17:23 (Box 7, Reel 1, Dvd 1)
  - Untitled Film Footage: Reel 2, 1937-1938; 1 Reels 16 mm; Duration: 22:24 (Box 7, Reel 2, Dvd 2)
  - Untitled Film Footage: Reel 3, 1937-1938; 1 Reels 16 mm; Duration: 14:16 (Box 7, Reel 3, Dvd 3)